[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
[The Romance of Hua Rong 2] [EP06]
[The Romance of Hua Rong 2] [EP06]
It's too sweet.
ًانها حلوة جدا.
I like it.
أحبها.
Rong
رونغ
This
هذه
is the lucky pastry I bought for you from Fan Building.
هي المعجنات المحظوظة التي اشتريتها لك من مبنى المعجبين.
It is said that
ويقال أن
a bite for each spouse
لدغة لكل من الزوجين
means a long and successful marriage.
يعني زواج طويل وناجح.
Why are you giving me your leftovers?
لماذا تعطيني بقايا طعامك؟
I won't eat it.
لن آكله.
I'm kidding.
أنا أمزح.
I wouldn't mind eating your leftovers.
لا أمانع في تناول بقايا طعامك.
Yummy.
لذيذ.
Rong
رونغ
Don't eat too full.
لا تأكل بشكل كامل.
We'll have something better later.
سيكون لدينا شيء أفضل لاحقًا.
There will be more?
سيكون هناك المزيد؟
Qin Shangcheng
تشين Shangcheng
Are you trying to fatten me up and break up with me？
هل تحاولين تسمني وتفتيتي
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
I've been pissing you off lately,
لقد كنت أزعجك مؤخرًا ،
and you've lost weight,
وفقدت الوزن ،
so I'm making it up to you.
لذا فأنا أعود إليك.
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
I'm not gonna eat anything from now on, anyway.
لن آكل أي شيء من الآن فصاعدًا ، على أي حال.
It said that
قال ذلك
the best dish in Hai City
أفضل طبق في هاي سيتي
is the sleeping fish soup.
هو حساء السمك النائم.
Those who don't eat it
أولئك الذين لا يأكلونه
will regret.
سوف يندم.
Okay, I'll just have a small bowl.
حسنًا ، سآخذ وعاءً صغيرًا فقط.
I'll take you there.
سآخذك إلى هناك.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
I get it, Qin Shangcheng.
فهمت ، تشين Shangcheng.
No wonder you know the place so well,
لا عجب أنك تعرف المكان جيدًا ،
even the special snacks,
حتى الوجبات الخفيفة الخاصة ،
'cause your foster father is the chief of Hai City
لأن والدك بالتبني هو رئيس مدينة هاي
and this is your hometown.
وهذه موطنك.
I take you here
آخذك إلى هنا
to show you
لتظهر لك
the place where I grew up.
المكان الذي نشأت فيه.
When I was a child,
عندما كنت طفلا،
my father would bring my mother and me
سيحضر والدي أمي وأنا
some sleeping fish soup
بعض حساء السمك النائم
whenever he returned from a sea trip.
كلما عاد من رحلة بحرية.
Over time,
متأخر , بعد فوات الوقت،
the sleeping fish soup
حساء السمك النائم
has become a taste of my hometown in my memory.
أصبح طعم مسقط رأسي في ذاكرتي.
This is your home when you are a kid.
هذا هو منزلك عندما تكون طفلاً.
Yeah.
نعم.
After all these years
بعد كل هذه السنوات
the yard is still the same.
الفناء لا يزال كما هو.
Since we left Hai City,
منذ أن غادرنا هاي سيتي ،
it has been uninhabited.
كانت غير مأهولة.
Why did you leave?
لماذا غادرت؟
After my foster mother's death,
بعد وفاة والدتي بالتبني ،
the Black Dragon Gang found my father's trace.
وجدت عصابة التنين الأسود أثر والدي.
Luckily, my father got the news first
لحسن الحظ ، حصل والدي على الأخبار أولاً
and took me away
وأخذني بعيدا
before they arrived.
قبل وصولهم.
When I was a child,
عندما كنت طفلا،
my foster father taught me swordplay here,
علمني والدي بالتبني لعب السيف هنا ،
but we left in such a hurry
لكننا غادرنا بسرعة
that we didn't take anything with us.
أننا لم نأخذ أي شيء معنا.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll be with you
سأكون معك
to bring back all your childhood memories.
لإعادة كل ذكريات طفولتك.
Okay.
تمام.
Look.
نظرة.
These were my treasures as a child.
كانت هذه كنوزي عندما كنت طفلة.
I can't believe the King Pirate
لا أستطيع أن أصدق قرصان الملك
has such a cute side.
لديه مثل هذا الجانب اللطيف.
Listen to this,
استمع الى هذا،
you can hear the sound of the sea in it.
يمكنك سماع صوت البحر فيه.
It's true.
انها حقيقة.
Amazing.
مدهش.
Number Riddles.
عدد الألغاز.
In this book
في هذا الكتاب
each number
كل رقم
has a corresponding word.
له كلمة مقابلة.
As a child,
كطفل،
I used to use these numbers
اعتدت على استخدام هذه الأرقام
to communicate with my friends in code.
للتواصل مع أصدقائي في الكود.
For example, four and five
على سبيل المثال ، أربعة وخمسة
means it's me.
يعني هذا أنا.
Then
ثم
Five, two and one means
خمسة ، اثنان وواحد
I love you.
أحبك.
Since Number Riddle is so fun,
نظرًا لأن Number Riddle ممتع جدًا ،
let's take it away
دعنا نأخذها بعيدا
and use it as our secret code from now on.
واستخدمه كرمز سري خاص بنا من الآن فصاعدًا.
Okay.
تمام.
This compass is for you
هذه البوصلة لك
so that you know where I am.
حتى تعرف مكاني.
Nonsense.
كلام فارغ.
This compass looks delicate.
هذه البوصلة تبدو حساسة.
Sharp eyes.
عيون حادة.
This compass
هذه البوصلة
and a boomerang come as a pair.
ويرتد كزوج.
This compass normally looks nothing special,
هذه البوصلة عادة لا تبدو مميزة ،
but it will automatically point to the boomerang
لكنه سيشير تلقائيًا إلى ذراع الرافعة
if the boomerang
إذا كان يرتد
appears within a mile.
يظهر في غضون ميل.
The boomerang of Swordman Yunhe?
بوميرانغ السياف يونهي؟
This is not a compass.
هذه ليست بوصلة.
This is "come to you".
هذا هو "تعال إليكم".
Where's the boomerang?
أين البمرنغ؟
The boomerang
بوميرانج
was accidentally lost
تم فقده عن طريق الخطأ
during the search for the Black Dragon Gang.
أثناء البحث عن عصابة التنين الأسود.
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
But don't be sad.
لكن لا تحزن.
We'll keep this compass on us
سنحتفظ بهذه البوصلة علينا
at all times from now on,
في جميع الأوقات من الآن فصاعدًا ،
and maybe we'll even find the boomerang.
وربما نجد بوميرانج.
I'll take this gift.
سآخذ هذه الهدية.
Okay.
تمام.
When I was a child,
عندما كنت طفلا،
my foster mother used to tell me that
كانت والدتي الحاضنة تخبرني بذلك
water was connected to all the seas
كانت المياه متصلة بكل البحار
and if I poured water on my body,
وإذا سكبت الماء على جسدي ،
I could feel
يمكن أن أشعر
my foster father
والدي بالتبني
who was sailing on the sea, missing us.
من كان يبحر على البحر فقدنا.
So I often played the water-sprinkling game with my foster mother
لذلك غالبًا ما كنت ألعب لعبة رش الماء مع والدتي الحاضنة
to kill the time.
لقتل الوقت.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Yeah.
نعم.
You little liar.
أيها الكاذب الصغير.
Play tricks with your husband.
العب الحيل مع زوجك.
Let me see what move you make next.
اسمحوا لي أن أرى ما الخطوة التي تتخذها بعد ذلك.
and I'll take that.
وسآخذ ذلك.
Look.
نظرة.
Do I look good?
هل ابدو جيدا؟
Pretty.
جميل.
I had no idea that my mother's clothes
لم يكن لدي أي فكرة عن ملابس أمي
would fit so well on you.
سوف تناسبك بشكل جيد.
It means I'm as fit as your foster mother.
هذا يعني أنني لائق مثل أمك الحاضنة.
By the way, Rong
بالمناسبة ، رونغ
today is the middle of the month,
اليوم منتصف الشهر ،
and my foster mother once said
وقالت والدتي الحاضنة ذات مرة
if people make a wish on the full moon,
إذا تمنى الناس اكتمال القمر ،
the wish may come true.
قد تتحقق الرغبة.
Do you want to have a try, Rong?
هل تريد المحاولة يا رونغ؟
Okay.
تمام.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Foster father and foster mother,
الأب بالتبني والأم الحاضنة ،
hope you
أتمنى لك
can bless Qin Shangcheng and me
يمكن أن يبارك تشين Shangcheng وأنا
as husband and wife,
كزوج وزوجة ،
never to be separated.
لا تنفصل ابدا.
Rong, what did you wish for just now?
رونغ ، ماذا كنت تتمنى الآن؟
I can't say.
لا استطيع ان اقول.
It doesn't come true if I say it.
لا يتحقق ذلك إذا قلت ذلك.
Let me guess.
دعني أخمن.
Did you wish that
هل تمنيت ذلك
you will be with me forever
ستكون معي إلى الأبد
and give me a warm home?
وتعطيني بيت دافئ؟
It was his own guess,
كان تخمينه ،
it had nothing to do with me.
لا علاقة لي به.
Foster father and foster mother,
الأب بالتبني والأم الحاضنة ،
please make it come true.
من فضلك اجعلها حقيقة.
A waste of a good look.
مضيعة لإلقاء نظرة جيدة.
Well.
نحن سوف.
Such grand courtesy for a first meeting.
هذه مجاملة كبيرة للاجتماع الأول.
But the courtesy
لكن المجاملة
is proper for us.
مناسب لنا.
Help me up now!
ساعدني الآن!
I don't want to hurt innocent people.
لا أريد أن أؤذي الأبرياء.
You
أنت
can stay there.
يمكن أن يبقى هناك.
come and get killed!
تعال وتقتل!
Kill me?
اقتلني؟
You guys?
شباب؟
No one has ever dared to speak to me like this.
لم يجرؤ أحد على التحدث معي بهذه الطريقة.
I am the number one master in Jingcheng.
أنا السيد الأول في Jingcheng.
I'll beat you to your knees and beg for mercy in a moment.
سأضربك على ركبتيك وأتوسل الرحمة بعد قليل.
Face your fate.
واجه مصيرك.
Get away!
ابتعد!
How dare you kick me!
كيف تجرؤ على ركلني!
Sixth Princess!
الأميرة السادسة!
You are the King Pirate, Qin Shangcheng,
أنت ملك القراصنة ، تشين شانغتشينغ ،
who tore up the imperial edict and proposed the imparity clause
الذي مزق المرسوم الإمبراطوري واقترح شرط عدم الوضوح
to my father.
إلى والدي.
Is that your reason for assassinating me?
هل هذا سبب اغتيالك؟
You are one of the few men
أنت واحد من الرجال القلائل
who have left my father at a loss for words.
الذين تركوا والدي في حيرة من الكلام.
I love you more than anything,
انا احبك اكثر من اي شئ،
so how could I kill you?
فكيف يمكنني قتلك؟
So
لذا
Sixth Princess
الأميرة السادسة
did you just play house?
هل لعبت في المنزل للتو؟
When I followed you,
عندما تابعتك ،
I saw you were inseparable.
رأيتك لا ينفصلان.
I didn't realize he wasn't your fiancé.
لم أدرك أنه لم يكن خطيبك.
Let me introduce him to you,
دعني أقدمه لك ،
he is my nephew.
انه ابن اخي.
As his aunt,
كخالته ،
I watched him grow up,
شاهدته يكبر ،
so our relationship is extremely good.
لذلك علاقتنا جيدة للغاية.
You are wrong, aunt.
أنت مخطئة يا عمة.
I am a few years older than you.
أنا أكبر منك بسنوات قليلة.
I watched you grow up.
لقد شاهدتك تكبر
Nothing different.
لا شيء مختلف.
Sixth Princess
الأميرة السادسة
so
لذا
It was Duanmu Bai you wanted to assassinate.
لقد كان Duanmu Bai الذي أردت اغتياله.
Yeah.
نعم.
It's all because Nie Yu is so stupid,
كل هذا بسبب أن ني يو غبي جدًا ،
otherwise, why would I do this?
وإلا فلماذا أفعل هذا؟
Nie Yu
ني يو
your fiancé-to-be?
خطيبك المستقبلي؟
With that emaciated body,
مع ذلك الجسم الهزيل ،
he couldn't even ride a horse,
لم يستطع حتى ركوب حصان ،
let alone marry me.
ناهيك عن الزواج بي.
The man I love
الرجل الذي أحبه
is a hero
بطل
like Qin.
مثل تشين.
One day,
يوم واحد،
he will fly to marry me
سوف يطير ليتزوجني
on a wooden kite.
على طائرة ورقية خشبية.
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
Qin Shangcheng's woman-attracting body
جسد تشين Shangcheng للمرأة
is acting up again.
يتصرف مرة أخرى.
So
لذا
Sixth Princess, you hope to assassinate Duanmu Bai
الأميرة السادسة ، تأمل في اغتيال دوانمو باي
to stop the hostage exchange
لوقف تبادل الرهائن
so that you wouldn't have to marry Nie Yu.
حتى لا تضطر إلى الزواج من ني يو.
Right.
الصحيح.
But you can't
لكن لا يمكنك ذلك
go to such an extreme.
اذهب إلى هذا الحد.
You are right, Rong.
أنت محق يا رونغ.
I shouldn't have been too impulsive.
لا ينبغي أن أكون مندفعًا جدًا.
But to avoid marrying someone I didn't know well,
ولكن لتجنب الزواج من شخص لم أكن أعرفه جيدًا ،
I had to join the bridal escort
اضطررت للانضمام إلى مرافقة الزفاف
before making other plans.
قبل وضع خطط أخرى.
Rong
رونغ
This is a vital thing in my life.
هذا شيء حيوي في حياتي.
You will help me, right?
سوف تساعدني ، أليس كذلك؟
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
Wait a minute.
انتظر دقيقة.
This little girl even wanted to stay,
حتى أن هذه الفتاة الصغيرة أرادت البقاء ،
she must want to stay with Qin Shangcheng.
يجب أن ترغب في البقاء مع تشين Shangcheng.
No way!
مستحيل!
I must extinguish the first hint
يجب أن أخمد التلميح الأول
of this danger.
من هذا الخطر.
When your husband
عند زوجك
is surrounded by admirers,
محاط بالمعجبين ،
don't be overly alarmed,
لا تنزعج كثيرا ،
instead show your grace
بدلا من إظهار نعمتك
and act like you don't care.
وتتصرف وكأنك لا تهتم.
This is playing hard-to-get.
هذا هو اللعب الذي يصعب الحصول عليه.
Rong, please grant my request.
رونغ ، من فضلك وافق على طلبي.
It's okay,
حسنا،
if you want to stay.
إذا كنت تريد البقاء.
But I have two requests.
لكن لدي طلبين.
First,
أولاً،
you must dress as a personal maid
يجب أن ترتدي ملابس خادمة شخصية
and stay by my side at all times.
وأبقى بجانبي في جميع الأوقات.
Second,
ثانيا،
You can no longer assassinate Duanmu Bai.
لم يعد بإمكانك اغتيال دوانمو باي.
But
ولكن
I can make sure you won't marry Nie Yu.
يمكنني التأكد من أنك لن تتزوج ني يو.
Do you agree, Sixth Princess?
هل توافق ، الأميرة السادسة؟
Yes.
نعم.
I knew you
كنت أعرفك
would love me the most.
سوف تحبني أكثر.
Then
ثم
In public,
علنا،
I serve you as a maid,
أنا أخدمك كخادمة ،
but in private,
ولكن على انفراد ،
you serve me.
انت تخدمني.
Nice try!
محاولة جيدة!
Change your clothes.
غير ملابسك.
Okay.
تمام.
I will follow your advice.
سوف اتبع نصيحتك.
Go.
يذهب.
Qin,
تشين ،
see you tomorrow.
أراك غدا.
Aren't you afraid of getting into trouble
ألا تخشى الوقوع في المشاكل
for keeping this spoiled princess around?
للحفاظ على هذه الأميرة المدللة حولها؟
It doesn’t matter.
لا يهم.
The troubles she made
المشاكل التي فعلتها
are not as many as Butterfly.
ليست كثيرة مثل الفراشة.
It won't affect me.
لن يؤثر علي.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Zhang, hurry up.
تشانغ ، أسرع.
You must explain it to Qin later.
يجب أن تشرحها لـ تشين لاحقًا.
Why do I always have to explain to him?
لماذا علي أن أشرح له دائما؟
I'm the one who takes the fall every time.
أنا من يأخذ السقوط في كل مرة.
Wait.
انتظر.
I'm six months older than you and I'm your second brother.
أنا أكبر منك بستة أشهر وأنا أخوك الثاني.
You said that we should share the blessings
قلتم أنه ينبغي لنا أن نشارك البركات
and you should take the blame,
وعليك أن تتحمل اللوم ،
have you forgotten?
هل نسيت؟
Well, you are right.
حسنًا ، أنت على حق.
Right?
حق؟
So
لذا
what do you think
ما رأيك
I should tell Qin?
يجب أن أقول تشين؟
You can be...
أنت تستطيع أن تكون...
My...My...Lord
بلدي ... يا ... يا رب
A...A...A spy
أ ... أ ... جاسوس
h...has infiltrated here.
ح ... تسللت إلى هنا.
Believe me.
صدقنى.
I'm sure Qin will believe you if you say that.
أنا متأكد من أن تشين سيصدقك إذا قلت ذلك.
Qian
تشيان
I don't even believe that,
أنا لا أصدق ذلك ،
let alone Qin.
ناهيك عن تشين.
What kind of spy
أي نوع من التجسس
would be able to infiltrate the heavily guarded Yun Hua Building?
ستكون قادرة على التسلل إلى مبنى Yun Hua شديد الحراسة؟
I think this person is suspicious
أعتقد أن هذا الشخص مريب
and probably a female spy.
وربما جاسوسة.
Stop.
قف.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Take off your veil.
اخلعي ​​حجابك.
It was the moment I met you
كانت اللحظة التي التقيت فيها بك
that I finally understood
التي فهمتها في النهاية
the meaning of love at first sight.
معنى الحب من اول نظرة.
I think I will lose sleep tonight,
أعتقد أنني سأفقد النوم الليلة ،
but I won't be counting sheep,
لكنني لن أحسب الغنم ،
I will only miss you.
سوف اشتاق لك فقط.
Who are you, wild boy?
من أنت أيها الفتى البري؟
How dare you be rude to a princess.
كيف تجرؤ على أن تكون وقحاً مع أميرة.
Princess? What princess?
أميرة؟  أي أميرة؟
Do you know this?
هل تعرف هذا؟
Your...your...your
الخاص بك ... الخاص بك ... الخاص بك
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
I'm
انا
the first counselor
المستشار الأول
of the King Pirate,
ملك القراصنة ،
Qian Dayou.
تشيان دايو.
I'm also King Pirate's good friend,
أنا أيضًا صديق King Pirate المقرب ،
You Daqian.
أنت دقيان.
So am I.
وكذلك أنا.
So you
وانت ايضا
are Rong and Qin's men.
هم رجال رونغ وكين.
Today,
اليوم،
I'm in a good mood.
أنا في مزاج جيد.
so I'll let you go.
لذلك سأتركك تذهب.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Qian!
تشيان!
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Love.
الحب.
This is love.
هذا هو الحب.
You're not even into a girl as good as Zhu.
أنت لست حتى في فتاة جيدة مثل Zhu.
She...
هي...
No.
رقم.
You don't understand.
أنت لا تفهم.
What I said before
ما قلته من قبل
is not love.
ليس حب.
I never found out
لم أكتشف الجواب قط
what
ماذا او ما
love at first sight was until today.
الحب من النظرة الأولى كان حتى اليوم.
Qian.
تشيان.
I am more worried that
أنا قلق أكثر من ذلك
you won't be able to carry
لن تكون قادرًا على حملها
this
هذه
royal love.
الحب الملكي.
You don't understand love.
أنت لا تفهم الحب.
Qian.
تشيان.
We are going to report to Qin.
سنقوم بإبلاغ تشين.
Yeah.
نعم.
Go, go, go.
إذهب! إذهب! إذهب.
Wake up!
استيقظ!
You don't understand.
أنت لا تفهم.
Wake up.
استيقظ.
My Lord
ربي
Here.
هنا.
Go.
يذهب.
My Lord
ربي
A...
أ...
Aunt.
عمة.
This is our uncle-in-law.
هذا هو عمنا.
My Lord
ربي
Your Highness
صاحب السمو
How are things going?
كيف تجري الامور؟
Are you two worried about
هل أنتما الاثنان قلقان بشأن
me finding out about the thing?
اكتشفت عن الشيء؟
No, no, no.
لا لا لا.
Well,
نحن سوف،
the most important thing
أهم شيء
between couples
بين الازواج
is trust.
هي الثقة.
So, there must be
لذا ، يجب أن يكون هناك
no secrets
لا اسرار
between you and Qin.
بينك وبين تشين.
Say it.
قلها.
Everything is under our lord's control.
كل شيء تحت سيطرة سيدنا.
Yeah.
نعم.
Everything
كل شىء
is under control.
تحت السيطرة.
At the very beginning,
بادئ ذي بدء،
we built a fortified point
بنينا نقطة محصنة
to lure Duanmu Bai into the trap.
لإغراء دوانمو باي في الفخ.
But we were robbed by the Qing Hong Gang!
لكننا تعرضنا للسرقة من قبل عصابة تشينغ هونغ!
What should we do?
ماذا علينا ان نفعل؟
Well.
نحن سوف.
Brothers.
الإخوة.
Earlier,
ابكر،
a guy
شخص
swore to me that
أقسم لي ذلك
this thing would be foolproof.
هذا الشيء سيكون مضمونًا.
Now, he has egg on his face.
الآن ، لديه بيضة على وجهه.
Why are you talking nonsense here?
لماذا تتحدث هراء هنا؟
You made me say it!
لقد جعلتني أقولها!
Why do you listen to me?
لماذا تستمع لي؟
Okay.
تمام.
The thing has happened.
لقد حدث الشيء.
What should we do next?
ماذا علينا أن نفعل بعد ذلك؟
Rong
رونغ
I think
أظن
This treasure chest was lost.
فقد صندوق الكنز هذا.
Someone will be more anxious than us.
سيكون شخص ما أكثر قلقا منا.
Yeah.
نعم.
Yeah, yeah.
نعم نعم.
I've investigated.
لقد حققت.
Tomorrow they will hold an auction
غدا سيعقدون مزاد
at the Qing Hong Villa.
في تشينغ هونغ فيلا.
And the stolen treasure
والكنز المسروق
is in the bidding.
في العطاء.
The Qing Hong Gang is too madcap.
عصابة تشينغ هونغ جنونية للغاية.
Not only did they steal our treasures,
لم يسرقوا كنوزنا فحسب ،
but they took them to auction.
لكنهم أخذوها إلى المزاد.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Obviously,
بوضوح،
their target is not the treasure
هدفهم ليس الكنز
but us.
لكننا.
In this case,
في هذه الحالة،
we have to go to the Qing Hong Villa.
علينا أن نذهب إلى تشينغ هونغ فيلا.
We should find a way to disguise our identities.
يجب أن نجد طريقة لإخفاء هوياتنا.
About the identities,
حول الهويات ،
my lord has already arranged.
رتبت ربي بالفعل.
The first pair
الزوج الأول
are the young master of the Mei Ying Tower,
هم السيد الشاب لبرج مي ينغ ،
Jian lai
جيان لاي
and his sister, Jian Wu.
وشقيقته جيان وو.
The second pair
الزوج الثاني
are the Death Couple,
هما زوجان الموت ،
Xie Lingyuan
شيه لينجيوان
and Zhao Yang.
و تشاو يانغ.
Wait, wait, wait.
انتظر انتظر انتظر.
Wait for a minute.
انتظر لدقيقه.
If we ran into them
إذا واجهناهم
and they revealed us,
وكشفوا عنا ،
wouldn't it be humiliating?
ألا يكون الأمر مهينًا؟
It'll be humiliating.
سيكون الأمر مهينًا.
Dead people won't show up.
لن يظهر الموتى.
South Desolation
الجنوب الخراب
is indeed a murderous and barbaric place.
هو بالفعل مكان قاتل وبربري.
You!
أنت!
What?
ماذا؟
These people are evil cultists.
هؤلاء الناس طائفيون أشرار.
What's wrong with my lord removing evil
ما الخطأ في إزالة ربي للشر
from the people?
من الناس؟
Okay, okay.
حسنا حسنا.
Get down to business.
ابدأ بالعمل.
At present,
في الوقت الحالي،
there's short of a woman.
هناك نقص في امرأة.
How about...
ماذا عن...
Ling
لينغ
would like to do you a favor.
يود أن يفعل لك معروفا.
She is...
هي تكون...
My new maid,
خادمتي الجديدة
Ling.
لينغ.
That's great.
ذلك رائع.
Lord
رب
and his aunt
وخالته
can play the couple.
يمكن أن تلعب الزوجين.
Ling and I
لينغ وأنا
can
يستطيع
play the brother and sister.
لعب الأخ والأخت.
No, it's improper.
لا ، هذا غير لائق.
My lady is unmarried.
سيدتي غير متزوجة.
If she and her nephew were to play a couple,
إذا لعبت هي وابن أختها دور زوجين ،
it would ruin her reputation.
من شأنه أن يفسد سمعتها.
I
أنا
would like to bear the blame for my lady
أود أن أتحمل اللوم على سيدتي
and defend my lady's reputation.
والدفاع عن سمعة سيدتي.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
What do you think, nephew?
ما رأيك يا ابن أخي؟
Rong's playing hard-to-get to
يلعب رونغ الذي يصعب الوصول إليه
test my attitude towards the matter
اختبر موقفي تجاه هذه المسألة
and take the initiative.
وأخذ زمام المبادرة.
I won't let her have her way.
لن أتركها تشق طريقها.
As a junior,
كصغير ،
I have no say in the matter.
ليس لدي رأي في هذا الموضوع.
Everything is at your disposal.
كل شيء تحت تصرفك.
You have a point, Ling.
أنت محق يا لينغ.
Heir and I are both from the official.
وريث وأنا على حد سواء من المسؤول.
Acting as people from Mei Ying Tower
يتصرفون كأشخاص من برج مي ينغ
can't be more proper for us.
لا يمكن أن يكون أكثر ملاءمة لنا.
Proper.
مناسب.
Hua Rong
هوا رونغ
still wants to attract me.
لا يزال يريد أن يجذبني.
So childish.
صبيانية جدا.
Why did this playing hard-to-get
لماذا كان هذا اللعب صعب المنال
turn out to be ineffective
تبين أنها غير فعالة
and put me in a difficult position?
ويضعني في موقف صعب؟
No sense!
لا احساس!
There must be something wrong.
لابد من وجود خطأ ما.
For playing hard-to-get,
للعب الذي يصعب الحصول عليه ،
the main point is
النقطة الرئيسية هي
to be sure of the balance.
للتأكد من التوازن.
Oh no, no, no.
أوه لا ، لا ، لا.
I must have acted too exaggeratedly
لابد أنني تصرفت بشكل مبالغ فيه
to make Qin Shangcheng think
لجعل تشين Shangcheng يفكر
I didn't care about it.
لم أهتم به.
Overdone is worse than undone!
المبالغة هي أسوأ من التراجع عنها!
I get an idea.
لدي فكرة.
The Qing Hong Gang
عصابة تشينغ هونغ
is a new force
هي قوة جديدة
that has emerged in the last two years.
التي ظهرت في العامين الماضيين.
It seems to
يبدو أنه
be a prestigious school,
أن تكون مدرسة مرموقة ،
but behind the scenes,
لكن وراء الكواليس ،
it is all about killing and smuggling,
الأمر كله يتعلق بالقتل والتهريب ،
and most of those items in this auction
ومعظم تلك العناصر في هذا المزاد
are of unknown origin.
من أصل غير معروف.
How dare they
كيف يجرؤون
do wrong under the nose of the King Pirate.
إرتكب خطأ تحت أنف الملك القراصنة.
Yeah.
نعم.
As soon as they come over,
بمجرد وصولهم ،
I'll kill two birds with one stone,
سأقتل عصفورين بحجر واحد ،
as a honeymoon gift for Rong.
كهدية شهر العسل لـ Rong.
Yeah.
نعم.
Don't worry!
لا تقلق!
Big Brother hasn't finished.
لم ينته الأخ الأكبر.
I know what he wants to say.
أنا أعرف ما يريد قوله.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'm sure I'll arrange it perfectly.
أنا متأكد من أنني سأرتب الأمر بشكل مثالي.
Qin Shangcheng
تشين Shangcheng
What's wrong.
ما هو الخطأ.
A midnight snack for you.
وجبة خفيفة في منتصف الليل لك.
Close the door.
أغلق الباب.
Rong, this is...
رونغ ، هذا ...
Sleeping fish soup.
حساء السمك النائم.
Sleeping fish soup?
حساء السمك النائم؟
The old chef has...
الشيف القديم لديه ...
It's not a problem for your wife.
إنها ليست مشكلة بالنسبة لزوجتك.
I ran all over the Hai City
ركضت في جميع أنحاء مدينة هاي
and finally found him in the south of the city.
وأخيرا وجدته في جنوب المدينة.
Try it.
جربها.
Is it the same taste as you were a kid?
هل هو نفس طعم كنت طفلا؟
Qin Shangcheng
تشين Shangcheng
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
I just feel a little guilty
أنا فقط أشعر بالقليل من الذنب
inside.
داخل.
After all,
بعد كل شيء،
I was angry with you before
كنت غاضبا منك من قبل
because of the royal intermarriage.
بسبب الزواج الملكي.
But you,
لكنك،
not only are you not mad at me for pretending to be a couple with the princess,
لست غاضبًا مني فقط لأنك تظاهرت بأنك ثنائي مع الأميرة ،
but you even brought me soup.
لكنك حتى أحضرت لي حساء.
You are a good wife.
انت زوجة صالحة.
Drink soup.
اشرب الحساء.
Okay.
تمام.
Take gentleness as my weapon.
خذ اللطف كسلاحي.
Pretend I'm a perfect and generous wife.
تظاهر أنني زوجة مثالية وكريمة.
In fact,
في الواقع،
I hide my blade point.
أخفي نقطة النصل.
Set me up as morally invincible.
جعلني أخلاقيا لا يقهر.
The fifth trick, a velvet paw,
الحيلة الخامسة ، مخلب مخملي ،
worked.
عمل.
Qin Shangcheng is already feeling guilty.
يشعر تشين Shangcheng بالذنب بالفعل.
He will definitely offer to change his group.
سيقدم بالتأكيد لتغيير مجموعته.
Honey.
عسل.
Don't be guilty.
لا تكن مذنبا.
As husband and wife,
كزوج وزوجة ،
we should understand each other
يجب أن نفهم بعضنا البعض
and trust each other.
ونثق في بعضنا البعض.
As you are so generous,
لأنك كريم جدا ،
I will
أنا سوف
never let you suffer again.
لا تدعك تعاني مرة أخرى.
I will gather everyone to regroup.
سأجمع الجميع لإعادة تجميع صفوفهم.
never betray
أبدا خيانة
your trust.
ثقتك.
Rong
رونغ
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
If there is anything wrong, tell me,
إذا كان هناك أي شيء خاطئ ، أخبرني ،
and I will listen to you.
وانا استمع اليك.
Nothing wrong.
لا شيء خطأ.
Everything goes well.
كل شيء يجري بشكل جيد.
The arrangement now is good.
الترتيب الآن جيد.
We are a couple.
نحن زوجين.
A model couple.
زوجان نموذجيان.
Chu Fengling is just a little girl.
Chu Fengling هي مجرد فتاة صغيرة.
I don't mind it at all.
أنا لا أمانع ذلك على الإطلاق.
Have some soup.
تناول بعض الحساء.
Qin
تشين
Why does she come?
لماذا أتت؟
Are you asleep, Qin?
هل أنت نائم يا تشين؟
I am just about to sleep.
أنا على وشك النوم.
It's good that you are not sleeping.
من الجيد أنك لا تنام.
I have something to ask you.
لدي شيء أن أسألك.
Qin
تشين
I'm troubled by a problem
أنا منزعج من مشكلة
and can't fall asleep.
ولا تستطيع النوم.
You have a rich Jianghu experience. [*The environment where the martial artists live.]
لديك تجربة جيانغو ثرية.  [* البيئة التي يعيش فيها فنانو الدفاع عن النفس.]
I'm sure you can solve my problem.
أنا متأكد من أنه يمكنك حل مشكلتي.
Well.
نحن سوف.
What's the problem?
ما هي المشكلة؟
Qin
تشين
If you like someone,
إذا أعجبك شخص ما ،
would you tell her?
هل تخبرها
I would.
أود.
Great minds think alike.
العقول العظيمة تفكر على حد سواء.
Qin
تشين
Marry me.
تزوجيني.
You and I have only known
أنت وأنا فقط عرفنا
for only a few hours
لبضع ساعات فقط
and you want to
وتريد
marry me?
تزوجيني؟
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
Duanmu Bai and Rong
دوانمو باي ورونغ
were engaged before they even met.
كانوا مخطوبين حتى قبل أن يلتقوا.
That's a different situation.
هذا وضع مختلف.
Duanmu Bai and I
دوانمو باي وأنا
aren't really getting married.
لا يتزوج حقا.
I'm not interested in being your husband.
أنا لست مهتمًا بأن أكون زوجك.
It's not a big deal.
لا مشكلة.
It makes me feel better
تجعلني اشعر بحال احسن
to get it off my chest.
لإخراجها من صدري.
If you don't like me today,
إذا كنت لا تحبني اليوم ،
I'll keep trying
سوف نستمر في المحاولة
and maybe you'll like me
وربما تحبني
after staying with me.
بعد مكوثي معي.
Who's there?
من هناك؟
Mice.
الفئران.
A group of mice came to my house recently.
جاءت مجموعة من الفئران إلى منزلي مؤخرًا.
They like stealing
يحبون السرقة
vinegar
خل
and sometimes climb into my bed.
وأحيانًا أتسلق إلى سريري.
I'll deal with it
سوف أتعامل معها
when you're gone.
متى ستذهبت.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll leave you
سوف اتركك
to catch the rats.
للقبض على الفئران.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Wait.
انتظر.
I need your help
انا بحاجة الى مساعدتكم
on a matter.
في مسألة.
Okay.
تمام.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
I also have a thing
أنا أيضا لدي شيء
to tell you.
لإخبارك.
You're the first person who dared to kick my butt.
أنت أول شخص تجرأ على ركل مؤخرتي.
You compare me to a mouse again.
تقارنني بالماوس مرة أخرى.
Rong
رونغ
Are you angry?
هل أنت غاضب؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
I'm just curious
أنا مجرد فضول
about what you said to the Princess just now.
حول ما قلته للأميرة للتو.
You'll know that tomorrow.
ستعرف ذلك غدًا.
Okay.
تمام.
Have a goodnight, my nephew.
ليلة سعيدة يا ابن أخي.
Don't reveal it to your little princess tomorrow.
لا تكشفها لأميرتك الصغيرة غدًا.
Okay.
تمام.
Remember to close the door
تذكر أن تغلق الباب
when you leave, my aunt.
عندما ترحل يا خالتي.
Okay.
تمام.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Qian
تشيان
From my experience of being married for years,
من تجربتي في الزواج لسنوات ،
the presence
وجود
of this princess
هذه الاميرة
is sure
مؤكد
to cause some trouble
لإحداث بعض المتاعب
between Qin and Rong.
بين تشين ورونغ.
Zhang
تشانغ
As one of the most charismatic men
كواحد من أكثر الرجال جاذبية
behind the Qin,
خلف تشين ،
it was time for me to step up
حان الوقت بالنسبة لي لأخذ خطوة
and take this culprit
وخذ هذا الجاني
into my pocket
في جيبي
and help out
والمساعدة
Qin and Rong.
تشين ورونغ.
Beware of your plans falling through.
احذر من فشل خططك.
Shut up.
اسكت.
- Just watch and see. - You...
- فقط شاهد وانظر.  - أنت...
Lord is in the room.
الرب في الغرفة.
You can't beat me.
لا يمكنك هزامي.
My lord,
ربي،
Hua Rong tried every possible way
حاول Hua Rong بكل طريقة ممكنة
to team up with you.
كفريق واحد معك.
You must be careful
يجب أن تكون حذرا
not to be confused by her.
لا ينبغي الخلط معها.
No way.
مستحيل.
She's just a mediocre woman,
إنها مجرد امرأة متواضعة ،
no better than a millionth of Little White Dove.
ليس أفضل من جزء من مليون من ليتل وايت دوف.
She wants me to like her.
هي تريدني أن أحبها.
It's a dream!
إنه حلم!
You are right, my lord.
أنت على حق يا مولاي.
Auntie, you don't look well.
عمتي ، أنت لا تبدو على ما يرام.
It seems you didn't rest well last night.
يبدو أنك لم ترتاح جيدًا الليلة الماضية.
No.
رقم.
Thanks to you.
شكرا لك.
I slept well.
لقد نمت جيدا.
Feeling good.
شعور جيد.
Since
حيث
gentle methods don't work on you,
الأساليب اللطيفة لا تعمل معك ،
I'll have to turn things around
سآخذ لتغيير الأمور
in a more ruthless way.
بطريقة أكثر قسوة.
Lai
لاي
Why are you eating like a child?
لماذا تأكل كالطفل؟
The food is all over your face.
الطعام يغطي وجهك بالكامل.
Come on.
هيا.
Let me give you a wipe.
دعني أعطيك مسح.
Miss Hua
ملكة جمال هوا
Please behave yourself in public.
يرجى التصرف في الأماكن العامة.
Okay, wipe it yourself.
حسنًا ، امسحها بنفسك.
Rong's using others to piss me off.
رونغ يستخدم الآخرين لإثارة غضبي.
She's getting bold.
لقد أصبحت جريئة.
Every dog has its day.
كل كلب له يومه.
Qin
تشين
This is green bean soup.
هذا حساء الفاصوليا الخضراء.
I bought it early in the morning at the Fan building.
اشتريتها في الصباح الباكر في مبنى Fan.
It clears heat and detoxifies the body,
يزيل الحرارة ويزيل السموم من الجسم ،
and eliminates heat and fire.
ويزيل الحرارة والنار.
Try it.
جربها.
Ling
لينغ
Don't forget your identity.
لا تنسى هويتك.
Thank you for reminding me, Rong.
شكرا لك لتذكيري يا رونغ.
Now,
حاليا،
Qin and I are a couple.
تشين وأنا زوجان.
I should feed him myself.
يجب أن أطعمه بنفسي.
Come on.
هيا.
Honey,
عسل،
have a try.
جرب حظك.
My aunt has been irascible lately.
كانت عمتي تغضب في الآونة الأخيرة.
She needs to eliminate fire more than I do.
إنها بحاجة إلى القضاء على النار أكثر مما أفعل.
Thank you, my nephew.
شكرا لك يا ابن أخي.
Wu
وو
With the grandeur of our Mei Ying Tower,
مع عظمة برج مي ينغ لدينا ،
how can you drink this cheap stuff?
كيف يمكنك أن تشرب هذه الأشياء الرخيصة؟
This top-notch diaphoretic pill,
هذه الحبة معرق من الدرجة الأولى ،
the Spring Pill,
حبة الربيع
is what you should take now.
هو ما يجب أن تأخذه الآن.
Lai
لاي
You are so considerate.
أنت متفهم جدا.
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
Lai
لاي
Is everything ready?
هل كل شيء جاهز؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
You see.
هل ترى.
Everything is here.
كل شيء هنا.
Everything in here
كل شيء هنا
represents a memory for us.
يمثل ذكرى لنا.
After ten years,
بعد عشر سنوات ،
we can dig it out
يمكننا اكتشافه
and recall the past together.
ونتذكر الماضي معًا.
You are so considerate, Rong.
أنت متفهم جدًا يا رونغ.
But this time box is too small.
لكن مربع الوقت هذا صغير جدًا.
The space is limited.
المساحة محدودة.
So, I just put in a few important things.
لذلك ، قمت فقط بوضع بعض الأشياء المهمة.
How about you?
ماذا عنك؟
What are you going to put in?
ماذا ستضع في؟
That's all?
هذا كل شئ؟
Just a small porcelain bottle?
مجرد زجاجة صغيرة من الخزف؟
As what you said,
كما قلت ،
there are too many memories between us.
بيننا ذكريات كثيرة.
We can’t put them all even we dig deep.
لا يمكننا وضعهم جميعًا حتى نحفر بعمق.
Hence
بالتالي
I put only the seeds of the balloon flower into it.
أضع فقط بذور زهرة البالون فيه.
I know you like balloon flowers.
أعلم أنك تحب زهور البالون.
It also witnesses our marriage.
كما يشهد زواجنا.
After ten years,
بعد عشر سنوات ،
I, you
I لك
and our children
وأطفالنا
can take the time box out together.
يمكن أن تأخذ مربع الوقت معا.
In time, our love
في الوقت المناسب حبنا
will blossom in the same way.
سوف تزهر بنفس الطريقة.
At that time
فى ذلك التوقيت
we can plant the balloon flowers,
يمكننا زرع زهور البالون ،
recalling the past
تذكر الماضي
and imagining the future together.
وتصور المستقبل معًا.
Okay, you barely pass the test.
حسنًا ، بالكاد تجتاز الاختبار.
Where are we burying this time box?
أين ندفن صندوق الوقت هذا؟
We can bury it
يمكننا دفنها
under a phoenix tree.
تحت شجرة طائر الفينيق.
The phoenix tree is called the tree of love.
تسمى شجرة العنقاء بشجرة الحب.
It symbolizes that we can be together forever.
إنه يرمز إلى أننا يمكن أن نكون معًا إلى الأبد.
Okay.
تمام.